I thank you all for giving Me this welcome….
Vi ringrazio tutti per avermi riservato questa accoglienza.
with such great love and respect
Tutti voi avete organizzato questo programma
you all have given this programme, I don't know
con così tanto amore e rispetto che non so
how much I have to thank you all, I don't understand.
come ringraziarvi, non capisco.
I wanted to thank you all
Volevo ringraziarvi tutti
for giving Me such a hearty welcome to Me today.
per avermi riservato questo caloroso benvenuto oggi.
I don't know what words to use to thank you.
Non so quali parole usare per ringraziarvi.
Today in every moment I am enjoying it.
Oggi gioisco di ogni momento.
I am very happy,
Sono molto felice,
what can I say to you all,
che cosa posso dire a tutti voi?
I don't understand.
Non capisco,
Your love and respect is beyond my strength,
il vostro amore e rispetto superano le mie forze,
beyond my expectation
le mie aspettative.
I don't understand why you are all
Non capisco perché mi stiate
embarrassing Me,
mettendo in imbarazzo,
I don't know what I have done for you all,
non so che cosa ho fatto per tutti voi.
the thing which you all wanted to have,
Avete avuto ciò
you have got it.
che volevate avere;
I haven't done anything for you all.
io non ho fatto niente per tutti voi.
I was overjoyed to see the way you all welcomed
Mi ha riempito di gioia vedere il modo in cui mi avete accolta
and you are singing songs of happiness and joy.
e state cantando canzoni di gioia e felicità.
I don't know how to express Myself
Non so come esprimermi
because I'm Myself very happy
poiché anch’io sono molto felice.
and I don't know what to say
E non so cosa dire
in your praise,
in vostra lode,
where you have taken to Sahaja Yoga
per esservi dedicati a Sahaja Yoga
so easily and have assimilated it.
con tanta facilità e per averlo assimilato.
Whatever it is,
Comunque sia,
it's a very mutual admiration society, I should say,
questa è una società di grande ammirazione reciproca, direi,
that we are enjoying each other.
in cui gioiamo gli uni degli altri.
May God bless you all
Che Dio vi benedica tutti
with this happiness and joy and complete oneness with the Divine.
con questa felicità, gioia e completa unione con il Divino.
Thank you very much, thank you.
Molte grazie, grazie.
Thank you
Grazie.